Um, are you having some
kind of lip seizure?
No, I'm trying to blend
coconut lip gloss
and pineapple lip gloss to
create a pina colada flavor.
I realize this isn't attractive.
Actually, it kind of is.
So, does it taste like pina colada?
Do you wanna find out?
Yes.
Eww.
Well?
You bent my teeth.
Hey.
Hey, can I borrow 30 bucks?
I gotta pay a cab driver.
You took a cab to school?
I had to.
My mom loaned her car to some
fisherman and I missed the bus.
A cab here from your
house doesn't cost $30.
It does if you make the
guy stop and buy you
a breakfast burrito.
[Honking]
Come on. Thirty bucks.
He's got the meter running.
Here's 20.
All I have is a 10 and
I need it-- you know,
I'm getting a little tired
of Sam "borrowing" money.
Why the air quotes around "borrowing"?
'Cause she never pays us back.
True. But don't be upset.
At least your lips smell
all girly and sweet.
They do not.
I wiped it off.
I just think it's kind of
lame for her to always
be hitting us up for cash.
Who's always hitting you up for cash?
You are.
Carly, am I always-- yes.
Okay, maybe I borrow money
a lot, but don't I always
pay back every-- no.
All right.
You guys figure out exactly
how much I owe you
Do you think she will?
I'll believe it when I see it.
Hey, here's that dxc cable you wanted.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Pina colada.
Hah.
[Growls]
[Music]
In five, four, three, two-- [Music]
I know you see
somehow the world
will change for me
and be so wonderful
live life, breathe air
I know somehow
we're gonna get there
and feel so wonderful
it's all for real
I'm telling you
just how I feel
so wake up
the members of my nation
it's your time to be
there's no chance
unless you take one
and the time to see
the brighter side
of every situation
some things are meant to be
so give your best
Ready?
Let's do this.
There they go.
Up to the ceiling.
And--pop.
[Screaming]
Not our best idea.
No.
'Sup?
Hey.
You ready to rehearse some "iCarly"?
Yup.
Is Sam here?
No, she's on her way.
We're gonna be upstairs rehearsing.
Don't harm yourselves.
[Doorbell]
Coming.
Well, hello there.
And hello there.
I'm Spencer.
Hi.
We live down the block
and I have been taking
Emily around to sell
sunshine girl fudge balls.
I love fudge balls.
Did you hear that, sweetie?
Why don't you ask the nice man
if he'd like to buy a box?
Yeah, just ask me.
I'm easy.
[Sobbing]
Oh, no.
Emily.
Did I--did I say something?
It's not you.
She's just so shy.
She's trying to sell
the most fudge balls
in her troop so she can win
this really cool bike.
Oh.
I could help her sell 'em.
Oh, I couldn't ask you to do that.
Oh, come on.
My little sister Carly
was a sunshine girl.
I used to help her sell
fudge balls all the time.
And you're sure you wanna help Emily?
How tall is your husband?
I'm single.
I really wanna help Emily.
[Music]
So, Fredwad, did you figure out
how much money I owe you guys?
You owe Carly and me exactly $526.
No way it's that much.
Show her.
Now, if you look at the graph,
you'll see that your borrowing
really took off two years
ago during July, then--
oh, you squished my tripod finger.
That's not something
a cool person says.
I don't care.
Are you gonna pay us back or what?
I was, but I didn't know
it was gonna be that much.
So how much do you have?
Um, let's see.
I've got 14 bucks, a AA
battery, some string, a fork,
and I think that's an olive.
The olive's moving.
I got it.
[Music]
Emily, come here, sweetie.
Spencer is going to tell
you how you guys can sell
a whole bunch of fudge balls, okay?
Okay, Emily, you and I are
gonna sit at this table
and whenever people walk
by us, we're gonna--
oh, no, no, Emily.
I-- oh, no, you go calm her down.
I got the fudge balls.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Emily. Emily.
Hey there, fudge balls?
No.
No? Okay.
How about you, ma'am?
Sunshine girl fudge balls?
No, thanks.
No. Hey, come on.
We got peanut butter.
We got caramel, marshmallow.
No.
No. Who's in a mood
for some fudge balls?
Girls, what's up?
Hey there, maybe you
girls didn't notice,
but I'm set up right over there.
I'm trying to help a
little girl win a bike.
Maybe we want a bike too.
Yeah, right.
See, here's the thing.
I don't think there's enough
customers around here for all of us.
And since I was here first,
I was thinking maybe
you guys could move-- [Music]
In five, four, three, two-- I'm Sam.
I'm Carly.
And this is "iCarly."
The only Web show that makes you laugh
and prevents heart disease.
So kick back with a pound of
bacon and enjoy the show.
To start off, Sam and I
are gonna perform a play
that she wrote herself
for drama class.
Miss Levinson gave me a d minus.
The play is called "the
prisoner who just wanted
"some soup and the man who
refused to give him some."
And action.
Just give me some soup.
I ain't gonna give you no soup.
Scene.
Thank you.
Hey, look, found a
dollar on the floor.
[Singing]
Anything can happen
on a live Web show
now, you just need to
find about 500 more.
Watch it, Fredward.
Sam and Freddie have been
fighting about money this week.
'Cause Sam owes Carly
and me over 500 bucks.
So if you wanna help me out
with that little problem,
send me some cash, care
of Ridgeway middle school
here in Seattle.
They ain't gonna send you no money.
They'll send me some money.
I forgive you for what you did
yesterday, but we need to talk.
Get out of here.
All I was trying to do
is help a little girl
sell enough fudge balls to
win a bike and I don't think
it was very sunshiny of you
girls to pick up my table
and just throw it into the
street like a-- no, wait.
No, not towards the car.
Oh, gee, stop.
Oh, my fudge balls.
This isn't over.
Sam.
What?
Principal Franklin wants you now.
What does he know about?
I don't know.
Oh, man.
Tell him I moved to Switzerland.
I'm gonna make a break for it.
Wait.
He knew you'd try to run.
He's got teachers posted at every
door all over the building.
Hey.
Tell Carly to meet me at
Franklin's office in two minutes.
What did you do?
I don't know.
But he always goes easier
on me when Carly's around.
It reminds him I'm not all bad.
Oh, wait.
What?
Lend me five bucks?
No.
[Music]
Hold on.
I'm not ready.
I'm waiting for someone.
Carly Shay, to the principal's office.
Principal Franklin.
You're looking well.
You join a gym?
Sam-- what happened?
Carly.
Look, principal Franklin,
it is my best friend Carly
who loves me and sees the
value in me as a person.
Right, Carls?
Tell the nice man.
Tell him what?
I sent you a text.
Oh.
Sam did nothing wrong.
She didn't do the thing
you're mad about.
She's not that kind of girf.
Girf?
Girl.
But you wrote girf.
Maybe you girfs have an
explanation for these?
What are those?
Letters sent to you
here at this school.
Apparently, they have something
to do with "iCarly."
Each one contains cash.
$10 from Sarah Cloody in Chicago?
Two bucks from Louis
Beckerman in New York.
Two bucks, way to dig deep, Louis.
This is serious.
Why?
Now, I can pay you and Freddie back.
No.
You can't solicit money from
kids over the Internet.
It's against the law.
This could get us in big trouble.
I suggest you return all
this money immediately.
Oh, man, do you know how
long it will take us
to send every one of these
kids their money back?
More mail.
We gotta send all those back too?
That's a lot of work for two girfs.
I hate this.
I hate this so much.
I can't believe this many
"iCarly" fans sent money in
just 'cause Sam asked them to.
It's gonna take us days
to send it all back.
Or weeks.
Hey, Sam, how are you coming with
those return address labels?
Good. Real good.
You're not making labels.
You're looking at trampolines.
I'm sorry.
I just want one so bad.
Well, you know when you
can have a trampoline?
When?
Never.
[Phone beeping]
I gotta go.
Oh, no.
You're not gonna go take
a nap while we sit here
working the mail-- I'm
not going to take a nap.
I got a job.
You got a job?
Where?
At chili my bowl.
Chili?
Yeah.
I figure if I gotta work,
it might as well be
around something I love.
Isn't chili my bowl the
place where some guy
found a finger in his chili last year?
It was a thumb.
Hey, Sam.
I'm in a bad mood.
You too.
Hi.
Hey.
You sell a bunch of fudge balls?
No.
How come he's selling fudge balls?
He's trying to help this little
sunshine girl win a new bike.
Hot mom.
Ah.
Why are you such a mess?
'Cause since those mean girls
pushed me out of my spot,
I tried moving my fudge ball
operation down by the shipyard.
And?
The dockworkers wanted no
part of me or my fudge balls.
They threw clams at me.
Ah.
Yeah.
You know, you don't have to
win that bike just to get
that sunshine girl's mom
to go out with you.
I know but I wanna sell more
than those rotten girls
at the market.
Hey, are you hungry?
Yeah, you bring home dinner?
Ah-huh.
What's in here?
Clams.
[Music]
Hey, lady.
Yes, can I help you?
I said I wanted hot sauce and
there wasn't no hot sauce
on my tray.
Sorry.
Here's some hot sauce.
You should have put it on
my tray in the first place.
You know where I wanna
put it right now?
You watch your mouth.
No, you watch your mouth
before I put my fist in it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You say you're sorry to the customer.
But he-- apologize.
I'm so very sorry.
You-- calm, calm, calm, calm.
You wanna keep this job?
No, but I need to.
Then behave.
Now, come here.
Here.
Now, go clean the men's room.
What?
Go clean-- no, no, no, no, no.
Don't say it again.
I, uh--I mean, can't you get
a guy employee to do it?
Now.
[Music]
[Toilet flushing]
[Burps]
Oh.
[Music]
Hey, what goes on?
What's up?
Hey.
What are you doing here so late?
Oh, I just thought I'd stop
by on my way home from work.
Oh, and Freddie, your
mom is looking for you.
Something about a sick relative.
What? I gotta go.
Which one of his relatives is sick?
None.
I made that up so he'd leave.
Why?
'Cause I don't want
Freddie to see me-- cry.
I don't like working.
I don't know how people do it.
It's horrible.
They don't let you sleep,
or watch TV, or go online.
And they expect you to be
nice to all the customers.
And I'm not even allowed
to eat the chili.
Do you know what its like
to be me, surrounded
by giant pots of chili and
not allowed to eat it?
I can't stand to see you like this.
You have to quit.
No, I can't.
I promised myself I wouldn't
quit till I pay back every Penny
I owe you and Freddie.
I had to clean urinals.
Boys are so gross.
You'll be okay.
My mom says none of my
relatives-- [Screams]
[Music]
Carly.
Carly, come down here.
Carly. Carly.
Spencer, it's 6:00 in the morning.
I know, but I've got big news.
I can't take you seriously
when you're wearing
duck pajama pants.
Duck boxers?
Tell me why you're sending all
this money back to your fans.
'Cause, principal Franklin
said it's not legal
to solicit money from
kids over the Internet.
Principal Franklin didn't go to
law school like your big bro.
You went for three days.
But I kept this book.
And it says, "it is
illegal to solicit money
"over the Internet from
persons under the age of 18."
We know that.
"Unless you provide a product
or service in return."
But we didn't provide
a product or service.
But you're going to.
Spencer.
"iCarly" is gonna provide
a product to every fan
that sent you guys money.
What products?
fudge balls.
[Music]
fudge balls?
Ah-huh. Balls of fudge.
And we can keep all the money?
Yup. It's totally legal.
So Spencer called Socko, got
a bunch of guys to come over
and they're sending out
fudge balls right now
to every "iCarly" fan
that sent us money.
Say, "yay."
But wait, the fudge balls aren't free.
No, but when you subtract
the cost of the fudge balls
from the money our fans sent us,
we still make $541 in profit.
And Spencer wins the bike for
the little sunshine girl.
But wait.
What do we do with the money?
Well, we get to keep 541
and Sam owes us 526,
so we give Sam the 526 and
then she can pay us back
and quit her stupid job.
But wait.
Stop saying, "but wait."
Sam is not gonna take
the money from us.
Why wouldn't she?
It's a pride thing.
It's why she won't quit her job.
If we just give her the
money, she won't feel like
she really paid us back.
Yeah.
Okay, how about this?
We find some adult
that Sam doesn't know.
Okay.
And we give him the 526 bucks and
then he gives the money to Sam
as a tip at the restaurant.
That's brilliant.
Isn't it?
But wait.
What?
That leaves an extra 15 bucks.
Yeah, five for me, five for
Sam, and five for you.
Go nuts.
[Music]
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Oh, look at-- can you see this?
Oh, look at these fries.
I have the money.
I have money.
Oh, oh, look. Oh, look.
Oh, look at this.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, hey, look.
I got money.
Money, money, money, money.
Woo-hoo. Woo.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hi.
I just wanted you girls to
know that I won the bike.
And because I am a
grownup, I forgive you
for behaving so rudely to me.
Take care.
[Music]
On the other hand, check
out how cool this bike is.
Oh, I won the fancy new
bike and you didn't.
How you jerks like me now?
Woo.
Oh, I'm out of control.
Oh, geez, I'm sorry. Oh.
What goes on, peoples?
Hey, where have you been?
Oh, I had little bid-ness
to take care of.
Bid-ness?
Yup. I kind of came
into a little money.
Like enough to pay us
back the $526 you owe us?
Like exactly that much.
Awesome.
Great.
So, where is it?
I spent it.
What?
Sam, you did not.
Yeah, I did.
You were supposed to pay us back.
Oh, you guys don't need that money.
I can't believe this.
You're insane.
I may be insane but I bought something
that's gonna be a lot of
fun for all three of us.
What'd you buy?
[Music]
Oh, great.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Surprise.
We're bouncing.
Hi.
Yeah.
Where is the couch?
[Music]
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0